keeptouch.net 2005-09-06

# Keeptouch Community Portal - Keeptouch Privacy Policy

Keeptouch has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [www.keeptouch.net](http://www.keeptouch.net/)

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and for other purposes. Logged IP address is used to track users as and when necessary, for example, when member has violated our Terms of Service or when required by law. 

**1\. Cookies**

Keeptouch uses cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Keeptouch also lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Keeptouch's cookies. 

**2\. Advertisers**

Our advertiser's ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our advertisers, and we do not have access to this information. 

**3\. Registration Forms**

Our site's registration forms requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and mailing address) and unique identifiers (NRIC number). 

The customer's contact information is used to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers, and to get in touch with the customer when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Unique identifiers (NRIC numbers) are collected from Web site visitors for use as membership ids in our membership record system. 

**4\. Order Forms**

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address). 

**5\. External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. Keeptouch is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**6\. Discussion Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**7\. Children's Guidelines**

This site DOES NOT MEET the Online Privacy Protection Act guidelines The following criteria are violated: 

This site allows children to post or distribute any personally identifiable information without first obtaining verifiable parental consent.  
This site does not provide children notice of what information is collected.  
This site des not encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online.  
This site does not allow the parent to obtain the information collected from the child and provide a way for the parent to prevent the future use of that information. 

**8\. Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us. 

**9\. Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [admin@keeptouch.net](mailto:admin@keeptouch.net)
